I get a lot of
comments and I want you to reply to me. The
main page of SBI General
is Arogya Plus policy for General whose premium is
fixed. Now you will also be surprised
how the prices are because the premium of all health
insurance is decided on a 60 basis,
so this policy is fixed
and similarly we will discuss
how it is fixed, whether the features of this line are
beneficial for you or not and
we will talk about everything that you need to know.
Before starting the video, I would
like to introduce myself. My
name is Gulhad Chiku. I am the first one. I have been in the
industry for the last six years with ASI
and I bring videos every week in
which I can make your personal life easy and better
because this is our company's side. This
sequence of policies does not run on them. This
entry is about General Arogya Policy. We will
talk about it first from the ability side. Individuals can get
both these policies. So,
they have Ind Plus four children one
policy.  Today's minimum balance in this three
month is 90 and maximum entries are 65 years.
Policy of life can be continued. You
can continue the policy as long as you want. There is a
strength of twenty three years in this policy.
After that, you will have to take a separate
policy by clicking on it. The policy term
option is one to three years. All three are available.
You can take a one year policy, two years policy, three years policy, two and a quarter
years
policy and if you take a three year policy, then you get a long term
discount. There is
80% discount on the two year policy and
7.5 percent discount on the three year policy. Here we will
talk about understanding. Tubelight Tilak is always available in this policy.
This
planetary bike is there for a very short time
because at this time four people including this oil red do
not have it. If you talk about long term
health insurance, then it is
not enough. There will be
no pre policy medical checkup in it. If
you do not have any medical history, then we will
talk about these hospitalizations.
Know the crop master  Before the expenses and the rest of the
express, the
emotions will ask for the expenses ring by
looking at the specific button. It happens that
due to the group of science, you come home from 7 in the morning to 7 in the evening
and 2014 hospitalization in which is
not necessary, then a
hair treatment related to it, you can claim 142 to 142 desserts in these
means of Pushpendra, the
news is Ayush, Ayurvedic, Yoga, Unani, Siddha
and Homeopathy, its hospitalization will be
₹ 2 lakhs, when is the domestic T20, he is
getting treatment at home, is in the condition
that he can go to the hospital, if he has to
apply in the hospital tomorrow, then there will be news up to 1 lakh rupees
in the admission list, there is
no romantic setting in it, there is no submit in it,
two more things are edited on it, your
OPD power is installed and it is printed for maternity, then there is the
word of expenses,
that covers up to speed limit, we will take it all, I don't remember, if you
see this, you will
understand for free that the cream is according to the OPD limit  It will be
defined, the
back side of Badoni limit is the same, emergency road
ambulance is in the news, ₹2 shift hospitalization
air ambulance is not in the news, we will take care of it,
now Jyoti Sunil will want a waiting ticket,
its waiting period is torn, which is
in the policy, you cannot get the hospitalization done in the queue for a long time,
from today maintain emergency response from the author, I do
not want to accept this system, do
not decide, if you already have any problem, whether it
is ours or a lifestyle problem, then the
latest hospitalization from it will not be in the news for four years
and there will be no constipation till the test match,
some specific mail message send, its
waiting ticket from the plane was on 24th March,
you can check the list, some things are in the
news after the first slaughter, some things one teaspoon,
after that we will see how the premium calculation is done, how
its premium is fixed, how the OPD is
decided, then it will be decided on two breaths,
first of all your family size and
your age, on that we will decide
how much your OPD will be,
your face will be in the form of a lens of that love, on its base, along with this  The
OPD benefit will be decided in front of you according to the size, so
suppose you have paid the premium which is different from Islam,
these will be the conscience, they do not have toxins,
after removing pimples and infections,
your tender comes in the fridge, that is why
if you are a tip and you are taking only your
individual policy then the
benefit will be there and because this is
between 4158 then you will get 2030 benefit,
this is your simple one, between life insurance and
education the premium is same
but OPD benefits will be charged like
yearly European benefit, then you can also add
that in Greater Noida for your benefit,
we take an example, if we take a premium of ₹1, then
Mitthu will go for
3030, then I will take the example
of an individual and between your 4158 then the
OPD benefit that you get is of this
₹500, if you go in this dish of 260 on the left side  If you
go, your premium will be saved
through the cafe, your toxins but your
OPD benefit will be reduced, there
are fifteen third, their premium is
2000, 3000,
1000 is included, I am 14.25 in this form,
I am tag, I get OPD benefit of ₹10, if I go
to MS Word Sector-16A Islam, then I get
₹5000 unwanted,
100 benefit and pea activated both
total share will be given, so maternity benefit
acid OPD benefit, so you can see
how much element is there for you, how much
benefit is there in this, but according to me,
if the sound is low then you should not watch Pran, then it
is not submitted, solve any questions regarding
this video, if you have any questions regarding
this plan, regarding this
day Arogya Plus, a lot of people had
demand for Islam, so I have recorded this plan
for you, if you want to ask anything about it,
then comment  Section, give me
anything, tell me anything,
suggestion on how to make the next video, tell me that too, a
constant reminder, before leaving, if
you are not subscribing to our channel then
please subscribe
because diet information and right time,
you will meet soon in the next video,
set it, the
last six years are premieres,
this morning itself there is merit,
leave it, do it
[music]
do it